# ADEPOJU ADEYEMI



adepojuadeyemi11@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/adeyemi-joshuaadepoju-3a0846189



647 677-1309



https://github.com/The-indigo

# Summary

Software developer armed with diverse experience in both web and mobile technologies. Has experience in mobile application development with Flutter, backend development with Express is and currently working with frontend technologies with Angular and React.js.

# **Experience**



## Flutter Mobile Developer

### OgaPos

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021 (3 months)

Converted ui designs into mobile apps with Flutter.

Responsible for Introducing and following the stacked architecture pattern for the projects.

Integrated Firebase through:

- i) Firebase authentication with phone number.
- ii) Firebase firestore for storing and retrieving application user data.

Integrated Local Storage with Sharedpreferences.

# Software Engineer Intern

### ZuriChat

Aug 2021 - Nov 2021 (4 months)

Converted ui designs into mobile apps with Flutter.

Worked with the backend developers to retrieve data from and store data to the backend through Api endpoints.

Refactored specific codebase as assigned by the team leads.

### Backend developer intern

### Hotels.Ng

Jun 2020 - Aug 2020 (3 months)

Wrote Micro Apis for certain services through the duration of the internship.

Wrote and performed tests to ensure code functionality.

Wrote Documentation for the Apis.

### **Education**



## Centennial College

Post graduate diploma, Software Engineering Technology

# Babcock University

Bsc, Computer Science Technology 2014 - 2018

# **Skills**

css • javascript • HTML5 • Angular • React.js • Flutter • Dart